NGUYEN TRAN PHUONG DUY

Software Engineer

👑 20/10/2000 | 📞 (+84) 966 740 812 | 🔀 duyntp2000@gmail.com | 😯 howznguyen

1 INTRODUCE

With many years of experience in web programming and has programmed many projects. I want to use these skills to contribute to the company and develop myself. I am a person who is always willing to learn new things and always try to do my best.

EDUCATION

= [2018-2022]

Ho Chi Minh City University of Food Industry (Software Technology)

(**P** GPA: 3.03/4.0)

© CAREER OBJECTIVE

Enhance my knowledge and capabilities by working in a dynamic environment.

Devote to knowledge and strength to the company.

Become a key and important member of the company during working time.

SOFT SKILLS

- Responsibility
- Self-learning
- ▼ Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Inventive
- Decisive
- Presentation

EXPERIENCE

曲 [12/2016 - 05/2022] ITRUM Forum - Founder

Founded a forum for IT students to share knowledge and experience. Managed and developed the forum.

苗 [04/2020 - Present] MindX Technology School - Programming Lecturer

Assisted in the instruction of lecture for web and game development. Instruct and guide students in using Scratch, GameMaker, HTML, CSS, JS, Firebase, Python.

苗 [07/2021 - 03/2024] Cube System Vietnam Co., Ltd - Software Engineer

Develop and maintain company projects.

Using PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, ExpressJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap to develop system.

苗 [08/2023 - Present] Korecent Solutions Pvt. - Freelancer Developer Develop and maintain company projects.

</> </> SKILLS

</> Layout & Design

5 HTML 를 CSS

Tailwind CSS

B Bootstrap

Programming Languages

Js JavaScript

TS TypeScript

PHP PHP

Python

PROJECTS

MSR [11/2021 - 02/2022]

Description: Website of Banking System **Technologies:** Angular, PostgreSQL, NodeJS **Role:** Front-end Developer, Manual Tester

🖸 Cube System Vietnam - HomePage [03/2022 - 04/2022]

Description: Develop a website of Cube System Vietnam.

Technologies: PHP, WordPress, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Role: Web Developer

SHIMADA Shoji Warehouse Management System [05/2022 -

10/2022]

Description: Develop a website for users, managers, and administrators to

manage the warehouse.

Technologies: PHP, Codelgniter, PostgreSQL, NodeJS (Socket.io)

Role: Web Developer, Database Designer, Test Automation

SBS [07/2022 - 08/2022]

Description: Develop a website for users, vehicles management

Technologies: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL

Role: Backend Developer, Database Designer

☑ ICONIC Survey [11/2022 - 01/2023]

Description: Develop a website for suvery, users, managers, and administrators

to manage the survey.

Technologies: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Docker, AWS

Role: Backend Developer, Frontend Developer, Database Designer, DevOps,

Pull Request Reviewer

CUBECOIN [04/2023- 03/2024]

Description: Maintain and develop the company's Blockchain virtual currency

system.

Technologies: Python, VueJS, Flutter, PostgreSQL, Go-Ethereum, AWS

(Lambda, S3, RDS, EC2, API Gateway)

Role: Backend Developer (Python), Frontend Developer (VueJS)

Framework











Database







Environments









Tools





NGUYỄN TRẦN PHƯƠNG DUY

Software Engineer

👑 20/10/2000 | 📞 (+84) 966 740 812 | 🔀 duyntp2000@gmail.com | 🗘 howznguyen

GIỚI THIỆU

Với kinh nghiệm lập trình Website nhiều năm và đã làm nhiều dự án khác nhau. Tôi muốn sử dụng kỹ năng và kiến thức của mình để đóng góp cho công ty cũng như phát triển bản thân. Tôi cũng là một người luôn sẵn sàng học hỏi những điều mới và luôn cố gắng làm hết sức mình.

MHOC VẤN

= [2018-2022]

Đại Học Công Nghiệp Thực Phẩm TP.HCM (Công Nghệ Phần Mềm)

(**E** GPA: 3.03/4.0)

Ø MỤC TIÊU

Mong muốn được làm việc trong môi trường chuyên nghiệp, năng động, nhiều cơ hội phát triển bản thân.

Cống hiến hết mình để đạt được mục tiêu của công ty.

Trở thành một thành viên chủ chốt và quan trọng của công ty trong thời gian làm việc.

F KŸ NĂNG MỀM

- Tinh thân trách nhiệm
- Tư học hỏi
- Làm viêc nhóm
- Linh hoat
- Giải quyết vấn đề
- ☑ Giao tiếp
- Sáng tạo
- Ra quyết định
- Thuyết trình

🖶 KINH NGHIỆM

苗 [2016 - 2022] ITRUM Forum - Sáng Lập

Thành lập diễn đàn để sinh viên CNTT chia sẻ kiến thức và kinh nghiệm.

Quản lý và phát triển diễn đàn.

苗 [2020 - Hiện tại] MindX Technology School - Giảng Viên Lập Trình

Hỗ trợ và hướng dẫn học viên trong việc phát triển Web và Game. Hướng dẫn học sinh sử dụng Scratch, GameMaker, HTML,CSS, JS, Firebase, Python.

苗 [07/2021 - 03/2024] Cube System Vietnam Co., Ltd - Kỹ Sư Phần Mèm

Phát triển và bảo trì các dự án của công ty.

Sử dụng PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, Python, ExpressJS, VueJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL trong việc bảo trì và phát triển hệ thống.

苗 [08/2023 - Hiên tai] Korecent Solutions Pvt. - Freelancer Developer

Phát triển và bảo trì các dự án của công ty.

</> </> KŸ NĂNG CHÍNH

</> Layout & Design

5 HTML **ᡦ** CSS

Tailwind CSS

B Bootstrap

Programming Languages

Js JavaScript

TS TypeScript

PHP PHP

PROJECTS

™SR [11/2021 - 02/2022]

Thông tin dự án: Website của hệ thống ngân hàng

Công nghệ: Angular, PostgreSQL, NodeJS **Vai trò:** Front-end Developer, Manual Tester

☑ Cube System Vietnam - Trang Chủ [03/2022 - 04/2022]

Thông tin dự án: Website của công ty Cube System Vietnam

Công nghệ: PHP, WordPress, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Vai trò: Web Developer

SHIMADA Shoji Warehouse Management System [05/2022 -

10/2022]

Thông tin dự án: Website quản lý kho hàng của công ty Shimada Shoji

Công nghệ: PHP, Codelgniter, PostgreSQL, NodeJS (Socket.io) **Vai trò:** Web Developer, Database Designer, Test Automation

SBS [07/2022 - 08/2022]

Thông tin dự án: Xây dựng website phục vụ người dùng, quản lý phương tiện

Công nghệ: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL **Vai trò:** Backend Developer, Database Designer

☑ ICONIC Survey [11/2022 - 01/2023]

Thông tin dự án: Xây dựng website phục vụ khảo sát

Công nghệ: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Docker, AWS

Vai trò: Backend Developer, Frontend Developer, Database Designer, DevOps,

Pull Request Reviewer

□ CUBECOIN [04/2023 - 03/2024]

Thông tin dự án: Bảo trì và phát triển hệ thống tiền ảo Blockchain của công ty.

Công nghệ: Python, VueJS, Flutter, PostgreSQL, Go-Ethereum, AWS (Lambda,

S3, RDS, EC2, API Gateway)

Vai trò: Backend Developer (Python), Frontend Developer (VueJS)

Framework







® ExpressJS





Database







Environments









Tools



